太空发射系统(SLS)芯级是当今世界最强火箭的主要结构
The Space Launch System’s Core Stage is the framework of the world’s most powerful rocket.
而在芯级被组装进SLS前
But before it’s assembled and integrated into SLS,
芯级的五个主要部分
the Core Stages five sections will need a
将由750个传感器、45英里的线缆和十万个紧固件组装起来
combination of more than 750 censors, 45 miles of cabling and 100,000 fasteners.
这么多东西都要仔细装好！咱们来瞅瞅
All that work is being done as we speak! Let’s take a closer look.
芯级底部是引擎段，装有四台RS-25发动机
At the base of the Core Stage sits the Engine Section, home to the four RS-25 engines,
这个结构将承受四台发动机的所有推力，内含总长18英里的线缆
the thrust structure they push against, as well as more than 18 miles of cables.
由于这个部分的复杂性，以及将要耐受的高温和剧烈震动
Because of this section’s complexity and the extreme temperatures and vibrations it will experience,
引擎段将装有500个传感器来监测各种情况
nearly 500 sensors are being installed in the engine section to monitor conditions.
芯级还有两组分开的燃料罐：液氢罐和液氧罐
The Core Stage contains two separate fuel sources: The Liquid Hydrogen Tank, and the Liquid Oxygen Tank.
总共容纳733000加仑(277万升)的燃料
Together, they hold a combination of 733,000 gallons of propellant.
低温燃料会让罐体在装有燃料的时候长度缩小6英寸(15厘米)
This fuel is kept so cold that it will actually shrink the tanks up to 6 inches in length
直径缩小超过1英寸(2.5厘米)
and more than 1 inch in diameter before they expand again as the fuel empties.
这使得所有直接连接到罐体的设备必须是
That means that anything attached to the tanks must be secured with a variety
“accordion-like”，意思是“像手风琴一样”
柔软或者可伸缩的结构
of flexible or accordion-like or telescoping connectors.
"Inter-"意思是“……之间的”，所以"Intertank"就是“燃料罐之间的”
Intertank是用来连接两个燃料罐的结构
The Intertank is designed to connect the two fuel tanks.
它不像SLS其他部分那样是焊接起来的
It isn’t being welded together like the rest of SLS.
而是由14500个特制螺栓、紧固件组装起来的
The Intertank is being put together by 14,500 custom bolts, fasteners, and fittings.
SLS的“大脑”在其最顶端
The “brain” of SLS is in its forward skirt section.
整个芯级上45英里的控制线缆最终都延伸到了芯级顶端部分
The 45 miles of cables controlling the SLS eventually lead to the forward skirt section,
三台飞行计算机监测1100个传感器，保证发射的顺利进行
where 3 flight computers monitor more than 1,100 sensors to ensure a successful flight.
计算机与芯级其他设备的供电来自于四块锂电池
Power for the computers and other core stage electronics is provided by four lithium ion batteries.
每块大小和汽车用的差不多
Each is about the size of an average car battery
能为火箭十分钟的飞行任务中提供1.8千瓦的功率
and provides about 1.8 kilowatts of power for the rocket’s 10-minute mission.
NASA的工程师正在加班加点做好每个零件，为这五个部件的装配与测试而努力
NASA Engineers are working hard as we speak to make sure that every part of the Core Stage is outfitted and tested.
但那也仅仅是开始
But that’s just the beginning.
一旦五个零件完成，还要把它们组装起来……
Once the individual sections are complete, the whole thing needs to be assembled…
而这以后有空再说吧。字幕翻译给虫，感谢观看！
But we’ll save that for another time. Thanks for watching!